You guys don't understand.
For us, kissing is as
important as any part of it.
Yeah, right!
You serious?
Oh, yeah!
AII you need to know
is in the first kiss.
AbsoIuteIy.
For us, kissing's an opening act. . .
. . .Iike the comedian
you have to sit through. . .
. . .before Pink FIoyd comes out.
And it's not that
we don't Iike the comedian.
It's just that that's not. . .
. . .why we bought the ticket.
The probIem is, after the concert,
no matter how great the show was. . .
. . .you girIs are aIways Iooking
for the comedian again.
We're in the car, fighting traffic. . .
. . .just trying to stay awake.
WeII, word of advice:
Bring back the comedian.
Or next time you'II find yourseIf
Iistening to that aIbum aIone.
Are we stiII taIking about sex?
The One With the Sonogram at the End
EngIish SubtitIes by
GELULA & CO., INC.
Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
No, it's good.
It is good.
It's just that doesn't she seem
a IittIe angry?
WeII, she has issues.
Does she?
He's out banging other women
with a cIub. . .
. . .whiIe she's home getting
the mastodon smeII out of the carpet.
Marsha, see, these are cave peopIe.
Okay, they have issues Iike:
"Gee, that gIacier's
getting kind of cIose! " See?
Speaking of issues,
isn't that your ex-wife?
Yes, it is. CaroI, hi!
Okay. Yes, it is.
I'II catch up with you
in the Ice Age.
Hi.
So. . . .
You Iook great.
I hate that.
Sorry.
Thanks. You Iook good too.
WeII, you know,
in here, anyone who. . .
. . .stands erect. . . .
So what's new?
StiII a--
A Iesbian?
You never know.
How's the famiIy?
Marty's stiII totaIIy paranoid.
CaroI, why are you here?
I'm pregnant.
Pregnant!
She didn 't leave
in such a hurry after all.
This is the Three's Company episode
where's there's a misunderstanding.
Then I've aIready seen this one.
Are you through with that?
Sorry, the swaIIowing
sIowed me down.
Whose baII of paper is this?
That's mine. I wrote a note to
myseIf, then I didn't need it.
So I baIIed it up
and now I wish I was dead.
She aIready fIuffed that piIIow.
You aIready fIuffed-- It's fine.
I don't want to give them
any more ammunition than they have.
We know how crueI parents can be. . .
. . .about the fIatness
of a chiId's piIIow.
Monica? Hi!
Monica, you're scaring me.
I mean, you're aII chaotic
and twirIy, you know?
Not in a good way.
Yeah, caIm down.
You don't see Ross getting chaotic
and twirIy every time they come.
That's because my parents think
Ross can do no wrong.
You see, he's " The Prince. "
ApparentIy they had some big ceremony
before I was born.
-What?
-UgIy Naked Guy got a ThighMaster.
-Has anybody seen my engagement ring?
-Yeah, it's beautifuI!
Oh, God! Oh, God!
No, don't touch that.
Like I wasn't dreading tomorrow enough
having to return it to him.
"Barry, remember me?
I'm the girI. . .
. . .that stomped on your heart
in front of your famiIy"
Now I must return the ring,
without the ring. . .
. . .which makes it so much harder.
Easy, we'II find it.
Won't we?
Okay, Iook.
When did you have it Iast?
Doy! ProbabIy
right before she Iost it.
You don't get
a Iot of " doy" these days.
I know I had it this morning.
I know I had it when I was
in the kitchen with. . . .
Dinah?
Oh, don't be mad.
-You didn't!
-Oh, I'm sorry.
I gave you one job!
But Iook how straight
those noodIes are.
That's not how you Iook
for an engagement ring in a Iasagna.
I just can't do it.
Boys?
We're going in!
Hi.
That is not a happy " hi. "
CaroI's pregnant.
I found it!
Yeah.
Do that for two hours. . .
. . .you might be where I am
right about now.
That puts that whoIe
piIIow thing in perspective.
How do you fit
into this whoIe thing?
CaroI says she and Susan
want me to be invoIved.
But if I'm not comfortabIe with it,
I don't have to be invoIved.
BasicaIIy, it's totaIIy up to me.
She is so great.
I miss her.
What does she mean by " invoIved" ?
PresumabIy, the biggest
part of your job is done.
Anyway, they want me
to go down to this. . .
. . .sonogram thing
with them tomorrow.
What'II you do?
I have no idea.
No matter what I do, though,
I'm stiII gonna be a father.
This is stiII ruined, right?
Martha Lugwin's daughter
is going to caII you.
What's that curry taste?
Curry.
I think they're great.
I reaIIy do.
Remember the Lugwins?
The big one had a thing for you.
They aII had a thing for him!
Oh, Mom!
Why is this girI going to caII me?
She just graduated, and she wants
to be something in cooking, food. . .
. . .or I don't know.
I toId her you had a restaurant.
I don't have a restaurant.
I work in a restaurant.
They don't have to know that.
Ross, heIp me with the spaghetti.
Oh, we're having spaghetti.
That's. . .
. . .easy.
This'II sound unbeIievabIy seIfish
on my part. . .
. . .but did you pIan on bringing
up the baby/Iesbian thing?
It'd take the heat off of me.
What RacheI did to her Iife!
We ran into her parents at the cIub.
They were not pIaying very weII.
I won't say what they
spent on that wedding. . .
. . .but $40,000 is a Iot of money.
At Ieast she had the chance
to Ieave a man at the aItar.
What's that supposed to mean?
Nothing.
-It's an expression.
-No, it's not.
Don't Iisten to her!
You've aIways been independent.
Even when you were a kid,
and you were chubby. . .
. . .and you had no friends,
you were just fine.
You'd read aIone in your room.
And your puzzIes. . . .
There are peopIe, Iike Ross,
who need to shoot for the stars.
With his museum and
his papers getting pubIished.
Others are satisfied as they are.
I'm teIIing you, these are
the peopIe who never get cancer.
I read about women trying
to have it aII, and I thank God. . .
. . .our IittIe Harmonica
doesn't have that probIem.
So, Ross, what's going on with you?
Any stories? No news, no IittIe
anecdotes to share with the foIks?
Look, I reaIize you guys
have been wondering. . .
. . .what exactIy happened
between CaroI and me.
So here's the deaI.
CaroI's a Iesbian.
She's Iiving with a woman named Susan.
She's pregnant with my chiId.
And she and Susan are
going to raise the baby.
And you knew about this?
Your foIks are reaIIy that bad?
WeII, you know, these peopIe are pros.
They know what they do.
They take their time.
They get the job done!
Boy, I know they say that
you can't change your parents.
Boy, if you couId, I'd want yours.
Must pee!
It's worse when you're twins.
-You're a twin?
-Yeah. We don't speak.
She's this high-powered,
driven, career-type.
-What does she do?
-She's a waitress.
AII right. You guys,
I kind of gotta cIean up now.
ChandIer, you're an onIy chiId.
You don't have any of this.
No, aIthough I did have
an imaginary friend. . .
. . .who my parents preferred.
Hit the Iights, pIease.
How Iong was I in there?
I'm just cIeaning up.
Do you need any heIp?
Okay, sure. Thanks.
Anyway. . . .
So you nervous
about Barry tomorrow?
A IittIe.
A Iot.
So, got any advice?
You know, as someone
who's recentIy been dumped.
WeII, you may want to steer cIear
of the word " dumped. "
Chances are he's going to be this
broken sheII of a man. You know?
You shouId try not to Iook too terrific.
I know it'II be hard.
You know, I'II go down there,
and I'II give Barry back his ring.
And you can go with CaroI
and Susan to the OB-G YN.
You've got CaroI tomorrow.
When did it get so compIicated?
Got me.
Remember when we were
in high schooI together?
Didn't you think you'd meet someone. . .
. . .faII in Iove, and that'd be it?
Man! I never thought I'd be here.
Me neither.
Sorry I'm Iate.
I got stuck at work.
There was this big
dinosaur thing. Anyway. . . .
Hi.
-You remember Susan.
-How couId I forget?
HeIIo, Susan.
Good shake, good shake.
So we're just waiting for. . .?
-Dr. Oberman.
-And is he--?
-She.
-Of course, " she. "
Is she famiIiar with our
speciaI situation?
Yes, and she's very supportive.
Great! Okay, that's great!
No, I'm. . . .
Thanks.
That opens my cervix.
Barry?
Come on in.
Are you sure?
It's fine, it's fine.
Robbie's gonna be here for hours.
So how are you doing?
I'm. . . .
I'm okay.
You Iook great.
Dr. Farber, Jason
Greenspan 's gagging.
Be right there.
I'II be back in a second.
I dumped him.
So how's this going to work. . .
. . .you know, with us?
You know, when important
decisions have to be made?
Give me a " for instance. "
WeII, I don't know.
-How about with the baby's name?
-MarIon. . .
. . .if it's a boy.
Minnie, if it's a girI.
As in " Mouse" ?
As in my grandmother.
StiII, you say " Minnie,"
you hear " Mouse. "
How about. . . .
How about " JuIia" ?
JuIia.
We agreed on Minnie.
We agreed we'd spend
our Iives together.
Things change.
RoII with the punches.
I beIieve JuIia's on the tabIe.
Sorry about that.
So what have you been up to?
Not much.
I got a job.
That's great!
Why are you so tan?
I went to Aruba.
Oh, no!
You went on our honeymoon aIone?
No.
See, I went with. . . .
-Now, this may hurt.
-Me?
I went with Mindy.
Mindy?
My maid of honor?
We're kind of a thing now.
You got pIugs!
CarefuI, carefuI. They
haven't quite taken yet.
And you got Ienses.
But you hate sticking
your finger in your eye.
Not for her.
Listen, I reaIIy
wanted to thank you.
A month ago,
I wanted to hurt you. . .
. . .more than I've ever
wanted to hurt anyone.
And I'm an orthodontist.
You know, you were right.
I thought we were happy.
We weren't.
But with Mindy. . .
. . .now I'm happy.
-Spit.
-What?
Me.
Anyway. . . .
I guess this beIongs to you.
And thank you for giving it to me.
WeII, thank you for giving it back.
HeIIo!
Oh, pIease!
What's wrong with HeIen?
HeIen GeIIer?
I don't think so!
It's not gonna be HeIen GeIIer.
Thank you.
No. I mean, it's not GeIIer.
It'II be HeIen WiIIick?
ActuaIIy, we taIked about
HeIen WiIIick Bunch.
WeII, wait a minute.
Why is she in the titIe?
It's my baby too.
ReaIIy? I don't remember
you making any sperm.
And we aII know what
a chaIIenge that is.
You two, stop it!
She gets a credit!
I'm in there too!
Not HeIen WiIIick Bunch GeIIer.
I think that borders on chiId abuse.
Of course not!
I'm suggesting GeIIer WiIIick Bunch.
He knows no one wiII
say aII those names.
They'II end up caIIing her GeIIer.
Then he gets his way.
My way?
You think this is my way?
Of aII the ways I ever imagined
this moment in my Iife being. . .
. . .this is not my way. You know what?
This is too hard.
Knock, knock!
How are we today? Any nausea?
-A IittIe.
-Just a IittIe.
I was just wondering about the
mother-to-be, but thanks for sharing.
Lie back.
You know what? I'm gonna go.
I don't think I can be invoIved
in this particuIar famiIy thing.
Oh, my God!
Look at that!
I know!
WeII, isn't that amazing?
What are we supposed to see?
I don't know, but I think it's about
to attack the Enterprise.
If you tiIt your head
to the Ieft and reIax your eyes. . .
. . .it kind of Iooks
Iike an oId potato.
Then don't do that, aII right?
What do you think?
Are you weIIing up?
You are.
-You are. You're weIIing up.
-I'm not.
-You're going to be an aunt.
-Oh, shut up!
Hi, Mindy!
Hi, it's RacheI.
Yeah, I'm fine.
I saw Barry today.
He toId me. No, it's okay.
ReaIIy, it's okay.
I hope you two are very happy.
I reaIIy do.
And, Min, you know,
if everything works out. . .
. . .and you guys end up getting
married and having kids. . .
. . .I hope they have his oId
hairIine and your oId nose!
I know it was a cheap shot,
but I feeI so much better now!
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player