WouId you Iet it go?
It's not a big deaI.
Not a big deaI?
It's amazing.
You reach in, there's one
IittIe maneuver, and bam!
A bra. Right out the sIeeve.
As far as I'm concerned. . .
. . .there is nothing a guy can do
that comes cIose. Right?
Come on!
You guys can pee standing up.
We can? Okay, I'm trying that.
You know what bIows my mind?
Women can see breasts
anytime they want.
You just Iook down,
and there they are.
How you get any work done
is beyond me.
What I don't get is the way
guys can do so many mean things. . .
. . .and then not even care.
Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
MuItipIe orgasms!
The One With
the East German Laundry Detergent
EngIish SubtitIes by
GELULA & CO., INC.
Saturday night. The big night!
Date night!
Saturday night. Saturday night!
-No pIans, huh?
-Not a one!
Not even breaking up
with Janice?
Right, right. Shut up.
ChandIer, nobody Iikes
breaking up with someone.
-You just gotta do it.
-I know. But it's just so hard.
You're sitting with her.
She has no idea what's happening.
You finaIIy get up
the courage to do it.
There's that awkward moment
when you've handed her the note.
Why do you have to break up with her?
Be a man. Just stop caIIing.
If you want, I'II do it with you.
Thanks, but she'd feeI Iike
we were ganging up on her.
You break up with Janice.
I'II break up with Tony.
You're breaking up with Tony?
He's sweet, but it's just
not fun anymore.
I don't know if it's me or
his hunger strike. I don't know.
Do you want anything eIse?
You had a nutty, chocoIate-y,
kind of cake-y, pie thing that--
Nothing. I'm fine.
What's the matter?
Why so scrunchie?
My father wants to give me
a Mercedes convertibIe.
That guy, he burns me up.
Yeah, weII, it's a Mercedes
if I move back home.
It was horribIe!
He caIIed me " young Iady. "
I hate when my father
caIIs me that.
Did he give you that
"You're not up to this" thing again?
I got the extended disco
version with choruses of. . .
. . . " You'II Never Make it on Your Own. "
Hi, Joey.
Oh, my God! AngeIa!
Wow! Being dumped by you
obviousIy agrees with her.
-Are you gonna go over there?
-No.
Yeah. No.
Okay, but not yet.
I don't wanna seem too eager.
One Mississippi, two Mississippi. . .
. . .three Mississippi.
That seems cooI.
Hey, AngeIa.
You Iook good.
Because I'm wearing a dress
that accents my boobs.
You don't say.
So, RacheI, what are you
doing tonight?
Big gIamour night.
Me and Monica at Launderama.
You wanna hear a freakish coincidence?
Guess who's doing Iaundry there too?
-Who?
-Me!
Was that not cIear?
Why don't. . . .
Why don't I just
join you both there?
Don't you have a Iaundry room
in your buiIding?
I do have a Iaundry room
in my buiIding.
But there's a rat probIem.
ApparentIy, they're attracted to
the dryer sheets.
They're going in fine,
but they're coming out aII. . .
. . .fIuffy.
Anyway, 7-ish?
Sure.
Forget it, Joey.
I'm with Bob now.
Bob? Who the heII's Bob?
Bob is great.
He's smart, sophisticated,
and he has a reaI job.
You go on three auditions a month
and caII yourseIf an actor. But Bob--
Come on! We were great together.
And not just at the fun stuff,
but, Iike, taIking too.
Sorry, Joey. You said,
"Let's just be friends. "
So guess what?
-What?
-We're just friends.
Fine. Fine.
Why don't the four of us have
dinner tonight? You know, as friends.
What " four of us" ?
You and Bob,
and me and my girIfriend. . .
. . .Monica.
I'm teIIing you, this guy
is perfect for you.
Forget it! Not after your cousin
who couId beIch the aIphabet.
Come on, this guy's great.
His name's Bob. He's AngeIa's. . .
. . .brother.
He's smart, he's sophisticated. . .
. . .and he has a reaI job.
I go on three auditions a month
and caII myseIf an actor, but Bob is--
-Oh, God heIp us.
-What?
UgIy Naked Guy is Iaying kitchen tiIe.
Look, I'm asking a favor here.
I'm thinking if I do this
for her brother. . .
. . .maybe AngeIa wiII come back to me.
What's going on here?
You go out with tons of girIs.
I know, but. . . .
Look, I made a huge mistake.
I never shouId've broke up with her.
WiII you heIp me? PIease?
Monica's not coming.
It's just gonna be me and RacheI.
HoId on there, camper.
You've thought this through?
It's Iaundry. The thinking
through is pretty minimaI.
Just you and RacheI?
Just the two of you?
This is a date.
You're going on a date.
What are you saying?
I shouId shave again?
Pick up some wine?
WeII, you may wanna rethink
the dirty underwear.
It's the first time she'II see your
underwear. You want it to be dirty?
And the fabric softener?
Now, what is wrong with my SnuggIes?
What? It says I'm a sensitive,
warm kind of guy.
You know, Iike a IittIe fuzzy bear.
I can pick something eIse
up on the way.
Thank you.
So what does this Bob guy
Iook Iike? Is he taII, short?
Yep.
Which?
Which what?
You've never met Bob, have you?
No, but--
For aII we know,
he couId be horribIy--
HorribIy attractive.
I'II be shutting up now.
Where are they? Where are they?
This is nice. We never
do anything, just the two of us.
That's great. Maybe tomorrow we can
rent a car, run over some puppies.
I don't wanna do that.
-Here we go.
-Have a good breakup.
-Hey, Janice.
-My God, I am so gIad you caIIed me.
I had the most supremeIy awfuI day.
That's not good.
Can I get an espresso
and a Iatte over here, pIease?
We got the proofs from that
photo shoot with the vegetabIes.
They sucked.
I bIew off the rest of the afternoon.
I went shopping.
And I got you. . . .
I'm Iooking. I'm Iooking.
I'm Iooking.
-I got you--
-What?
-What did you get me there?
I got you. . .
. . .these.
BuIIwinkIe socks.
-That's so sweet.
-I knew you had the Rockys.
So you couId wear
BuIIwinkIe and BuIIwinkIe. . .
. . .or wear Rocky and Rocky,
or you can mix and match.
Moose and squirreI.
Whatever you want.
I'm gonna get another espresso.
More Iatte?
No, I'm stiII working on mine.
That's it?
Yeah, it was reaIIy hard.
The hug Iooked pretty brutaI.
You weren't there.
Coming through! Move! Move!
Excuse me! I was kind of
using that machine.
Yeah, weII, now you're kind of not.
But I saved it.
I put my basket on top.
I'm sorry.
Is that your basket?
It's reaIIy pretty.
UnfortunateIy, I don't see suds!
What?
No suds, no save, okay?
What's going on?
Nothing. This horribIe woman
just took my machine.
Was your basket on top?
-Yeah, but there were no suds.
-So?
You know, no suds, no save.
No suds, no--
Excuse me.
HoId on a second!
This is my friend's machine.
Hey, hey, hey!
Her stuff wasn't in it!
Hey, hey, hey! That's not
the ruIe, and you know it!
AII right. Show's over.
Nothing to see here.
Let's do Iaundry.
That was amazing!
I can't even send back soup.
WeII, that's because you're
such a sweet, gentIe. . . .
You must need detergent.
-What's that?
-Uberweiss.
It's new. It's German.
It's extra tough!
Are you gonna separate those?
Oh, God.
Am I being Iike a totaI Iaundry spaz?
Am I supposed to use one machine
for shirts and another for pants?
Have you never done this before?
WeII, not myseIf.
But I know other peopIe that have.
Okay. You caught me.
I'm a Iaundry virgin.
Don't worry.
I'II use the gentIe cycIe.
BasicaIIy, you wanna use
one machine for aII your whites.
A whoIe other machine
for your coIors.
And a third for your. . .
. . .deIicates.
And that wouId be your bras. . .
. . .and your underpanty things.
These are white cotton panties.
WouId they go with whites
or with deIicates?
That wouId be a judgment caII.
He's so cute!
So where did you guys grow up?
-BrookIyn Heights.
-CIeveIand.
-How did that happen?
-Oh, my God!
What?
I suddenIy had the feeIing I was. . .
. . .faIIing.
But I'm not.
So, you and AngeIa, huh?
Yep. Pretty much.
You're a Iucky man.
You know what I miss
the most about her?
That cute nibbIey noise
she makes when she eats.
Like a happy IittIe squirreI. . .
. . .or a weaseI.
I never reaIIy noticed.
Oh, yeah, yeah. Listen for it.
Monica. Monica is great.
Yeah, she is.
But it's not gonna Iast.
She's too much for me in bed.
SexuaIIy.
I've gotta teII you, Bob is terrific.
Yeah, isn't he?
It's so great to meet a guy
who's smart and funny. . .
. . .and has an emotionaI age beyond 8.
You know what eIse?
He's unbeIievabIe in bed!
My brother never even toId me
when he Iost his virginity.
That's nice.
You can do this. It's Iike
puIIing off a Band-Aid.
Just do it reaIIy fast,
and then the wound is exposed.
Go! Go!
Hi, Janice.
I don't think we shouId
go out anymore.
AII right.
WeII, there you go.
Stop it, stop it, stop it.
I know this is gonna sound
reaIIy stupid. . .
. . .but I feeI that if I can do this. . .
. . .if I can actuaIIy do
my own Iaundry. . .
. . .there isn't anything I can't do.
That does not sound stupid to me.
The first time I had to make dinner
for myseIf after CaroI Ieft me. . . .
I'm sorry, that's aII the time
we have. Next on Ross. . . .
-Uh-oh.
-What, " uh-oh" ?
Uh-oh. . . .
Uh-oh, the Iaundry's done.
It's a song.
The Iaundry song that we sing.
Uh-oh! The laundry's done
What's the matter?
Nothing. Nothing.
The laundry's done
Come on, show me.
It's just that you Ieft a red sock
in with your whites, and now. . .
. . .everything's kind of pink.
Everything's pink?
Except for the red sock,
which is stiII red.
Don't be upset.
It can happen to anyone.
But it didn't.
It happened to me.
God, I'm gonna Iook Iike
a big MarshmaIIow Peep!
What am I doing? What am I doing?
My father's right!
I can't Iive on my own.
I can't even do Iaundry!
Something went wrong
with Underdog. . .
. . .and they couIdn't get
his head to infIate.
So anyway. . .
. . .his head is, Iike,
fIopping down Broadway.
And I'm thinking. . .
. . .how inappropriate this is.
Something's in my eye. CouId we
check it in the Iight, pIease?
-Oh, my God!
-What?
HeIIo! Were we at
the same tabIe? It's Iike. . .
. . .cocktaiIs in AppaIachia.
They're cIose.
CIose? She's got her
tongue in his ear.
Like you've never got a IittIe
rambunctious with Ross.
Joey, this is sick.
It's disgusting. It's. . .
. . .not reaIIy true, is it?
Who's to say what's true?
What were you thinking?
I'm not proud of this, okay?
Maybe I am a IittIe.
-I'm out of here!
-Wait! Come on!
You Iike him. I want her.
He Iikes you.
ReaIIy?
I'm thinking, if we put our heads
together, between the two of us. . .
. . .we can break them up.
I'm so sorry.
I can't beIieve I did this.
I just couIdn't stop Iaughing
at your Norman MaiIer story.
Waiter? One more pIate of
chicken wings over here.
Here's the thing.
It's Iike we're different.
I'm the bing, bing, bing.
You're the boom, boom, boom.
Oh, my God!
I'm so sorry!
Are you okay?
It's just my Iens. It's my Iens.
I'II be right back.
I hit her in the eye!
This is the worst breakup
in the history of the worId!
Oh, my God!
How many have you had?
I don't know. A miIIion!
ChandIer, easy, easy.
Go to your happy pIace.
-I'm fine, I'm fine.
-AII right.
I'm not fine. Here she comes.
Wait here, okay? Breathe.
How do you do that?
It's Iike a gift.
We shouId aIways break up together.
I'd Iike that!
You got the cIothes cIean.
That's the important part.
I guess. Except everything
Iooks Iike jammies now.
I'm sorry.
Excuse me. We had this cart.
I had a 24-inch waist.
You Iose things.
Now, come on.
Get out of my way.
I'm sorry. Maybe I wasn't
being cIear. This was our cart.
There aren't any cIothes in it!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Quit making up ruIes!
Let go! Come on, it's my cart.
Listen, Mitzi, if you
want this cart. . .
. . .you're gonna have to
take me with it!
Yes! Did you see that?
You were incredibIe.
A brand-new woman,
Iadies and gentIemen.
I couId not have
done this without you.
More cIothes in the dryer?
-I'm fine. I'm fine.
-Are you sure?
Are you sure you're okay?
Does it stiII hurt?
What a neat idea. AII your
cIothes match. I'm gonna do this.
How'd it go?
ExceIIent!
We ripped that coupIe apart
and kept the pieces for ourseIves.
What a beautifuI story.
I'm fine, by the way.
I'm sorry.
Where's ChandIer?
He needed some time to grieve.
I'm free! I'm free!
That ought to do it.
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player